Hey, everybody. Welcome to this A1
English listening practice video. You
can use this video to practice your
listening and comprehension as I speak.
Before we start, remember to download
the Listening Time podcast. And if you
want my specialized training, then
become a member at
patreon.com/listeningtime.
If you become a member, then you'll get
my seminars where I train you to listen
more effectively and understand native
speakers. And if you become a Listening
Time family member, then you'll receive
my advanced podcast, which will help you
reach an advanced level of listening.
Okay, today we're going to talk about
some different countries. And
specifically, I'm going to talk about
some countries that I've traveled to.
This video will have a part two, so I
can talk more about these countries. So,
the first country I want to talk about
is Mexico. This is where I live. Mexico
has almost 130 million people. It's a
big country. I've been to many different
cities here. Some of my favorite cities
are Guadalajara, Guanajuato, and Mexico
City. Mexico also has some really
beautiful nature. People love traveling
to Mexico to spend some time at the
beach because there are some amazing
beaches here. The water is really warm,
and so is the weather. Okay, next I want
to talk about France. This is the first
country that I ever traveled to in
Europe, but unfortunately, I've only
been to Paris. I haven't been to any
other cities there. However, I love the
city of Paris. Since one of my favorite
activities is walking, Paris is the
perfect city for me to travel to.
You could walk for days and days
throughout the city without getting
bored. I think Paris is one of the most
beautiful cities in the world. I love
the architecture, the history, and the
general feeling of the city.
There are so many nice places to see
there, but I know that there are a lot
of other interesting places to visit in
France. I hope that I can travel all
around the country in the future. Okay,
next I want to talk about Portugal. I
had the opportunity to spend two weeks
in this awesome country. I went to three
different cities when I was there,
Lisbon, Porto, and Braga. The capital,
Lisbon, is a really interesting place to
visit. I especially loved walking
through the old parts of the city, and
the city of Porto was one of my favorite
cities that I visited. It's one of the
most beautiful cities I've ever seen. I
loved watching the sun go down over the
river in the evening, and I really
enjoyed taking a boat on the river, too.
Overall, I thought Portugal was a
fantastic country to travel to, and I
recommend it to you. Lastly, let's talk
about Spain. I spent more than two weeks
in Spain, and I visited six different
cities. The first places we visited in
Spain were in the south of the country.
The south of Spain is really unique. The
culture there is a little different from
the culture in the other parts of Spain.
I really enjoyed my time in Sevilla and
Granada and I would love to go back. I
also really liked Madrid, but I only
stayed there for two nights. If I go
back to Spain, I'm definitely going to
spend more time in this city. It was
also cool to travel along the
Mediterranean coast. We took a train
from Valencia to Barcelona and we really
enjoyed the view. I think that a lot of
people want to live in Spain because of
the sea, the weather, and the food. By
the way, I loved the ham that I ate in
Spain. They have the best ham in the
world. Okay, that's all for today. I'll
make a part two to this video and I'll
talk about a few other countries that
I've traveled to. Remember to download
my free Listening Time podcast and
become a member at
patreon.com/listeningtime
to receive my specialized training to
help you understand native speakers. And
if you want to reach an advanced level
of listening, then become a Listening
Time family member to receive my
advanced podcast. The link is in the
description below this video. Also,
subscribe to the channel, click on the
bell, and follow us on Instagram. I'll
see you next time.